Guide to the University Historical Material records, 1821-2012 RG0031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Scrapbooks, journals, diaries, 1901-1972; RG0031 Series 18; 2 Linear feet (Flat box 75, Box 53, Box 50, Box 47, Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook of E.K. Morris, 1933 -1960 (Flat box 75, Folder 1)
    Materials in this collection includes one scrapbook of clippings, letters, and photos covering various subjects: Boy's Club of Washington [including an autographed photo and letter from J. Edgar Hoover] (1945-1960); GW baseball team which Morris coached (1933-1942); Berkshire School and St. Alban's school events; and Kiwanis club activities (1946-1960). The materials in the scrapbook range in date from 1933-60 and was donated to the University Archives by Eleanor DeAngelis (widow of Vincent DeAngelis, former Professor of Physical Education at GW) in 2003. Formerly ACC#1045.
    Edward Karrick Morris (1897-1981) founded the Federal Storage Company in Washington, and was a long time Trustee of the The George Washington University, serving from 1956-72 (Chairman from 1965-72).
    Known as E.K., Mr. Morris was born on January 25, 1897 in New York City. He received his education in Massachusetts at the Berkshire School and later Williams College. After serving in U.S. Naval Aviation in World War I, and then as Director of Athletics at the Berkshire School, he became a resident of Washington, D.C. He married Teresa James in 1924 and in 1925 founded the Federal Storage Company, serving as its president for thirty-eight years, until it merged with the Security Storage Company of Washington in 1963. He was named Chairman of the Board of the consolidated corporation and served until his retirement in 1966. Morris became a Trustee of George Washington University in 1957, was elected Chairman in 1965, and Chairman Emeritus in 1972.
    Mr. Morris served as President of the following civic organizations: Washington Executives Association (!940-41); Boy's Clubs of Greater Washington (1948-50); Kiwanis Club of Washington (1952-53); United Givers Fund of the National Capital Area (1956-58); Greater Washington Board of Trade (1959-60); National Capital Area Foundation (1959-60); Boy's Club Foundation (1961-62); Berkshire School General Alumni Association; Williams College Alumni Club of Washington. He was also master of Temple-Noyes Masonic Lodge.
    Morris was an Advisory Director of the Riggs National Bank, Director and member of the Executive Committee of the Washington Gas Light Company for eighteen years, Chairman of the Victory Van Corporation for eighteen year, and the Liberty National Bank for twenty years.
    Mr. Morris was also a member of the Executive Committee of the Consortium of Universities of Washington, Chairman of the Luther Rice Society at GW, and Chairman of the Executive Committee of the Episcopal Home for Children. For ten years he served as a member of the Board of Governors of St. Albans School, and was a trustee of the Better Business Bureau, Federal City Council, and the National Capital Downtown Committee. He was a Vice President of the Association of Oldest Inhabitants of the District of Columbia, Director of the Young Men's Christian Association of Metropolitan Washington, and member of the Advisory Board of the National Capital Area Council of the Boy Scouts of America. He was also a member of Sigma Phi, Omicron Delta Kappa, Alpha Kappa Psi, and Alpha Phi Omega fraternities.
    Mr. Morris received an honorary Doctorate of Laws from Southeastern University in 1956, a Brotherhood Award from the National Conference of Christian and Jews in 1957, Silver Keystone Award of the Boy's Clubs of America in 1970, and an honorary degree of Doctor of Public Service from GW in 1973. In addition to this incredible involvement with the community, E.K. Morris also served as the baseball coach at GW from 1933-42. He died November 20, 1981 in Washington, D.C.
  - Index to photocopied scrapbook, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    This folder contains an index of topics that are found in a photocopied scrapbook of newspaper clippings concerning people and events in GW history. They range in date from 1903 to 1910. They were transfered to the University Archives in 2001 from the University Relation department. See also Acc 887 and 940. Formerly Acc 596.
  - Miscellaneous pages of a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    This folder contains miscellaneous pages that were found in a photocopied scrapbook of newspaper clippings concerning people and events in GW history. They range in date from 1903 to 1910. They were transfered to the University Archives in 2001 from the University Relation department. See also Acc 887 and 940. Formerly Acc 596.
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    This folder contains photocopied newspaper clippings that were found in a scrapbook concerning people and events in GW history. They range in date from 1903 to 1910. They were transfered to the University Archives in 2001 from the University Relation department. See also Acc 887 and 940. Formerly Acc 596.
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 31)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 33)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 34)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 35)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 37)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 38)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 40)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 41)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 42)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 43)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 44)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 45)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 46)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 47)
  - Newspaper clippings from a photocopied scrapbook on GW history, 1903 -1910 (Box 88, Folder 48)
  - Sponge hippo, 2000 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    This is a Soft sponge "Hippo" given out at opening Convocation at the George Washington University, Fall 2000. Formerly Acc#943, item 68.
  - Autograph book of quotations belonging to book binder and GW faculty member, Marian U. M. Lane, 1941; Series 18; 1 vol.
    Biographical / Historical
    Born in England, Lane learned the art of book binding and illumination as a young girl and spent two years working in a small studio for Henry James. She later settled in Washington, D.C., working out of her apartment at 1851 Columbia Road. She was an Assistant in Applied Design at The George Washington University from 1907 to 1909. She also gave private lessons out of her home/studio, and practiced the art of bookbinding. Her most famous commissions were books for Queen Elizabeth of Belgium and the Emperor of Japan. Following a heart attack in the mid-1950s, Lane gave up bookbinding, but taught classes in illumination until 1960. She wrote and bound the All Hallows Guild Book for the National Cathedral, and produced Christmas cards for the Cathedral, one of which became a "best seller" with over 300,000 reproductions sold in one year. She was a founding member of the Miniature Painters, Sculptors, and Gravers Society of Washington, D.C.
    Unbound book belonging to Marian U. M. Lane (1874-1963) containing a collection of hand-written quotations.
- Newspapers, magazines, publications, 1821-2006; RG0031 Series 19; 6 Linear feet (Box 51, Flat box 58, Box 266, Box 52, Box 59, Box 54, Box 57, Box 56, Box 55, Box 62, Box 88, Box 99, Flat box 70)
  The collection in this series contains newspaper clippings, newsletters, student handbooks, programs, pamphlets, articles, journals, magazines, student newspapers, and university publications. They range in date from 1821 to 2006. This series concerns the history of GW School of Medicine.
  Please note that in addition to the Foggy Bottom News issues listed here, there is an additional set (1958-2004) cataloged as part of the Special Collections Research Center's holdings, which can be found by searching the library catalog.
  - Women's rifle team newspaper clippings, 1927 -1996 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    A collection of newspaper clippings concerning George Washington University's women's rifle team. These news clippings from local newspapers concern events and activities of the rifle team. They range in date from 1927-1930. Also included is a letter dated Oct. 26, 1996 from Betty Clark, team manager and coach, to the University Archivist donating these materials.
    Formerly Acc 625.
  - Student handbook, 1928 -1929 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Student handbooks donated to University Archives by alumni Ross Bundy, A.B. 1932 (via Greenwald) in 1998. Formerly Acc#681.
  - Student handbook, 1929 -1930 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Student handbook, 1930 -1931 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Student handbook, 1931 -1932 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Student handbook, 1935 -1936 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    The other copy in this folder is a gift of Linda Tigner, August 2014 (2014.035).
    Ms. Tigner donated this item on behalf of her father Milo Tigner who attended GWU from 1935-1938.
  - Student handbook, 1939 -1940 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Student handbook, 1942 -1943 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Student handbooks donated to University Archives by alumni Ross Bundy, A.B. 1932 (via Greenwald) in 1998. 2 copies of 1942/43. Formerly Acc#681.
  - GW Bulletin, Summer 1929 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    Bulletins donated to University Archives by alumni Ross Bundy, A.B. 1932 (via Greenwald) in 1998. Formerly Acc#681.
  - GW Bulletin, Summer 1931 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - GW Bulletin, 1938 -1939 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Convocation program, 02/09/1929 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    Convocation program donated to University Archives by alumni Ross Bundy, A.B. 1932 (via Greenwald) in 1998. Formerly Acc#681.
  - Univ.[ersity] exam schedule supplement, 1930 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    Exam schedule supplement donated to University Archives by alumni Ross Bundy, A.B. 1932 (via Greenwald) in 1998. Formerly Acc#681.
  - GW basketball schedule, 1933 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Basektball schedule donated to University Archives by alumni Ross Bundy, A.B. 1932 (via Greenwald) in 1998. Formerly Acc#681.
  - Troubador's program of "Sometime Soon,", 1929 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Troubador's program of "Sometime Soon" donated to University Archives by alumni Ross Bundy, A.B. 1932 (via Greenwald) in 1998. Formerly Acc#681.
  - GW Athletic review: Mt. St. Marys vs. GWU, 09/21/1941 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    Football program donated to University Archives by alumni Ross Bundy, A.B. 1932 (via Greenwald) in 1998. Formerly Acc#681.
  - The Weekly Columbian, 10/10/1903 --05/18/1904 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Bound volume of The Columbian Weekly newspaper, "published every Saturday in the interests of Columbian University." Volume1:1-v.1:30 (Oct. 10, 1903-May 18, 1904). Index to contents in University Archives.
    Formerly Acc#405.
  - The Weekly Columbian, 10/17/1903 --05/18/1904 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Bound volume of The Columbian Weekly newspaper, "published every Saturday in the interests of Columbian University." Volume1:2-v.1:30 (Oct. 17, 1903-May 18, 1904). Includes advertisements in front and back covers. Index to contents in University Archives. Formerly Acc#405.
  - Foggy Bottom News, 02/1958 --10/1973 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    The "Foggy Bottom News" (1958-2004), the neighborhood newspaper of the area, was donated to the collection as a result of the 1996 exhibit the Foggy Bottom Association and the Gelman Library sponsored called "Fantastic Foggy Bottom: The Growth of a Community." The exhibit was designed in conjunction with GW's 175th Anniversary, and a committee was formed to collect and choose materials for inclusion in the exhibit. The newspaper documents to a high degree the interaction of the community with The George Washington University, which moved to the Foggy Bottom area in 1912. Generally, it was published monthly. Ellie Becker was the editor of the paper from 1989-2004, when publication ceased. It was revived in December 2005 by its new editor, Michael Malloy. This set of publications range in date from February 1958 to October 1973. They were donated to the University Archives in 2004 by the editor of the paper, Ellie Becker. Formerly Acc 553.
  - Foggy Bottom News, 11/1973 --12/1991 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    The "Foggy Bottom News" (1958-2004), the neighborhood newspaper of the area, was donated to the collection as a result of the 1996 exhibit the Foggy Bottom Association and the Gelman Library sponsored called "Fantastic Foggy Bottom: The Growth of a Community." The exhibit was designed in conjunction with GW's 175th Anniversary, and a committee was formed to collect and choose materials for inclusion in the exhibit. The newspaper documents to a high degree the interaction of the community with The George Washington University, which moved to the Foggy Bottom area in 1912. Generally, it was published monthly. Ellie Becker was the editor of the paper from 1989-2004, when publication ceased. It was revived in December 2005 by its new editor, Michael Malloy. This set of publications range in date from Nov. 1973 to Dec. 1973. They were donated to the University Archives in 2004 by the editor of the paper, Ellie Becker. Formerly Acc 553.
  - Foggy Bottom News, 02/1992 --10/2000 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Foggy Bottom News, 11/2000 --07/2004 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Foggy Bottom News, 12/14/2005 --2006 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    The "Foggy Bottom News" (1958-2004), the neighborhood newspaper of the area, was donated to the collection as a result of the 1996 exhibit the Foggy Bottom Association and the Gelman Library sponsored called "Fantastic Foggy Bottom: The Growth of a Community." The exhibit was designed in conjunction with GW's 175th Anniversary, and a committee was formed to collect and choose materials for inclusion in the exhibit. The newspaper documents to a high degree the interaction of the community with The George Washington University, which moved to the Foggy Bottom area in 1912. Generally, it was published monthly. Ellie Becker was the editor of the paper from 1989-2004, when publication ceased (formerly Acc#553). It was revived in December 2005 as a newsletter by its new editor, Michael Malloy. This set of publications range in date from Dec. 14 2005 to 2006.
  - Columbian Call, 11/13/1895 --05/10/1897 (Flat box 58, Folder 1)
    Student newspaper. Index in University Archives. Formerly Acc#404.
    Bound copy#1 of Volume I (complete): Begins: November 13, 1895, vol. 1 no. 1 Ends: June 6, 1896, vol. 1 no. 26
    Bound copy#2 of Volume I (complete): Begins: November 13, 1895, vol. 1 no. 1 Ends: June 6, 1896, vol. 1 no. 26
    Loose copies of Volume II: November 21, 1896 vol. II no.1 (2) November 28, 1896 vol. II no. 2 (2) December 5, 1896 vol. II no. 3 (2) December 12, 1896 vol. II no. 4 (2) December 23, 1896 vol. II no. 5 (2) January 8, 1897 vol. II no. 6 (2) January 30, 1897 vol. II no. 8 (2) February 8, 1897 vol. II no. 9 February 17, 1897 vol. II no. 10 March 2, 1897 vol. II no. 11 March 23, 1897 vol. II no. 12 May 10, 1897 vol. II no.13
    Missing: 1897 vol. II no.7
    Extra loose copies of Volume I: November 13, 1895 vol. I no. 1 (2) November 27, 1895 vol. I no. 3 December 4, 1895 vol. I no. 4 December 11, 1895 vol. I no. 5 (2) December 18, 1895 vol. I no. 6 January 2, 1896 vol. I no. 7 January 16, 1896 vol. I no. 9 January 23, 1896 vol. I no. 10 January 30, 1896 vol. I no. 11 (2) February 8, 1896 vol. I no. 12 February 15, 1896 vol. I no. 13 (2) February 22, 1896 vol. I no. 14 February 29, 1896 vol. I no. 15 (2) March 7, 1896 vol. I no. 16 March 14, 1896 vol. I no. 17 March 21, 1896 vol. I no. 18 March 28, 1896 vol. I no. 19 (2) April 4, 1896 vol. I no. 20 April 11, 1896 vol. I no. 21 (2) April 24, 1896 vol. I no. 22 (2) May 2, 1896 vol. I no. 23 May 9, 1896 vol. I no. 24 (2) May 21, 1896 vol. I no. 25 (2) June 6, 1896 vol. I no. 26 (2)
  - Columbian Call, 11/16/1897 --05/03/1898 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Student newspaper. Index in University Archives. November 16, 1897 vol. III no. 1; December 1, 1897 vol. III no. 2 (2); December 15, 1897 vol. III no. 3 (2); January 5, 1898 vol. III no. 4 (2); January 18, 1898 vol. III no. 5 (2); February 1, 1898 vol. III no. 6 (2); February 15, 1898 vol. III no. 7; March 1, 1898 vol. III no. 8; March 15, 1898 vol. III no. 9; April 19, 1898 vol. III no. 11; May 3, 1898 vol. III no. 12 (2)
    Formerly Acc#404.
  - Football programs, GW vs. South Dakota, 10/17/1930 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Materials in this collection include football programs belonging to William Helvestine. They range in date from 1930-35, and were donated to the University Archives by Joan C. Netherwood in January 2005.
    Acc#2005.002; formerly MS2000
  - Football programs, GW vs. Dickinson, 10/25/1930 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Football programs, GW vs. New York Aggies, 11/08/1930 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Football programs, GW vs. Albright, 11/15/1930 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Football programs, GW vs. Catholic University, 11/22/1930 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Football programs, GW vs. Navy, 11/29/1930 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Fraternities - The Circle (Omicron Delta Journal), 06/1934-12/1934 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Materials in this collection include journals and news clippings belonging to William Helvestine. They range in date from 1930-35, and were donated to the University Archives by Joan C. Netherwood in January 2005.
  - Fraternities - The Surveyor (journal of Acadia fraternity), 1931 -1934 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Magazine - College Humor, 01/1934 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Materials in this collection include journals belonging to William Helvestine. They range in date from 1930-35, and were donated to the University Archives by Joan C. Netherwood in January 2005.
  - Personal - news clipping, Mason Lodge card, GWU emblem, 1935 ca. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Independent Chronicle and Boston Patriot, 02/07/1821 (Flat box 70, Folder 1)
    Dispatch from the National Intelligencer on page 2: column 4 stating that the charter for Columbian College had been approved by both Houses of Congress. Concerns that it may be devoted to Baptist sectarian purposes are explained as a reason passage was delayed. Formerly Acc#963.
  - National Intelligencer, 01/15/1822 (Flat box 70, Folder 2)
    News on page 3: column 5 describes the inauguration of the faculty of Columbian College, and lists their names. Formerly Acc#963.
  - U.S. Telegraph, 11/15/1826 (Flat box 70, Folder 3)
    Luther Rice, President of the Board of Trustees, accuses Baron Stow, editor of the Columbian Star, of slandering him. Copy 1. Formerly Acc#963.
  - U.S. Telegraph, 11/15/1826 (Flat box 70, Folder 4)
    Luther Rice, President of the Board of Trustees, accuses Baron Stow, editor of the Columbian Star, of slandering him. Copy 2. Formerly Acc#963.
  - National Intelligencer, 05/01/1828 (Flat box 70, Folder 5)
    Announcement of commencement Dec. 14, 1828 on page 3:column 3. Formerly ACC#963.
  - "GW Medicine", 1967 -1971 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    This folder includes "GW Medicine" magazines from Fall 1967- Winter 1971. Donated by Clarence R. Hartman. Formerly Acc#201.
  - "GW Medicine", 1972 -1974 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    This folder includes "GW Medicine" magazines from Spring-Summer 1972- Winter 1974. Donated by Clarence R. Hartman. Formerly Acc#201.
  - "GW Medicine", 1975 -1977 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    This folder includes "GW Medicine" magazines from Spring 1975- Winter 1977. Donated by Clarence R. Hartman. Formerly Acc#201.
  - "GW Medicine", 1977 -1979 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    This folder includes "GW Medicine" magazines from Fall 1977- Fall 1979 (special survey issue). Donated by Clarence R. Hartman. Formerly Acc#201.
  - "GW Medicine", 1979 -1980 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    This folder includes "GW Medicine" magazines from Winter 1979- Winter 1980. Donated by Clarence R. Hartman. Formerly Acc#201.
  - "Courier" medical magazine, 1961 -1964 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    This folder includes "Courier" issues from March 1961, June 1961, fall 1962, and summer 1964. The "Courier" is a George Washington University Medical Center magazine. Donated by Clarence R. Hartman. Formerly Acc#201.